Due to extreme fatigue and malnutrition resulted from not eating.
She has been suffering from serious deprivation of body fluids.
So it would be better to keep quiet.
You are making things no fun at all like this.
Get up!
Come around! Kang Yoo Jung.
Oh, you woke up, Kang Yoo Jung!
-Let's go! -Yes sir!
This really sucks!
Don't want another girl to die because of me.
It is not your fault, sir!
-I am not asking your opinion. Mind your own business –sorry, sir.
Shut up!
She asked you to bring them here like this?
You don't make a penny, yet still want to help others
This is why I'm going crazy.
Is Insuk nobody? she is my sister.
And also your sister in law.
Anyway, we have to buy fish in other shops even if not from hers.
She said her business was not going well, so i bought some.
No big deal!
So finally a brother in need.
Selling fish for decades, she has never sent us anything for free.
Yes, times are hard for them,
I am no better either, not good at all! ok?
Mom,
Are we too poor to afford some seafood?
No, I didn't mean that!
There are only 3 of us.
What your father bought is far too much for us.
A prosecutor is nobody.
I have to work very hard, but never is the salary raised.
So, let it be!
Why not find a wealthy woman who can open a law office for me to get married?
I will see to it if you are serious.
Bullshit!
Oops! Do not yell at me!
Fuck!
Are you going to flirt with the rich just for a so-called comfortable life?
It is always my hope that you can finally become a upright prosecutor and
do justice for those who are poor and wronged.
I am afraid that I failed to meet your expectation.
So are you going to give up, then?
You will achieve no success if you give up so easily because of the little hardships.
So how about you, dad?
Why do you finally quit?
What?
Do Hoon!
Thanks to your abandoned life,
I have never thought about other ways of living,
and have been living like this regrdless of others,
because I wanted to achieve your dream and make up for your life.
Do you know how I maintain this position?
Do you really konw how hard to stick to it till now?
But look at me!
Look at you two, quarrelling bitterly over those petty fish!
I am not the great prosecutor as mother thinks,
nor the upright one in dad's mind.
I cannot do anything on my own.
Do Hoon...
Se Yeon, running a hotel is never an easy task.
If i think so, i will not be here asking your help, president!
Others think I will lead a easy life by painting,
but my actual job was smiling
and sucking up to other people in place of my father.
And now I have got appropriate education in how to get along with others.
With only 14.2% of the shares that Min Hyuk holds,
it's hard to retain K Hotel.
I'm going to be part of your family soon.
Sir, please give me the purchsed shares of hotel by K Construction.
I heard you got the hotel shares from may dad.
I just get what I deserve.
Our marriage is a business.
And that thing the other day...
The thing I practised for many days,
but you just walked away regardless of me.
Or the thing you came back proposing with a cheap ring,
asking me for help.
Or that
you brougt the girl who killed your girlfriend to me.
Listen to me.
I've tried to understand you.
Would I have done the same thing if you were dead?
Maybe for a while,
I would cry and be upset.
But you've been doing this for years. It's an obsession.
Shut up!
And this obsession is of no help to you,
and that girl
Shut up! Shin Se Yeon!
Stop now! Even so, Seo Ji Hee will
definitely understand you.
So stop now! Don't be furious at others.
I said "shut up"!
And it is so childish of you to
find Kang Yoo Jung blindly.
Do you really think Seo Ji Hee will appreciate it
if you batter that poor girl?
Shin Se Yeon! I told you to stop!
Good! just yell at me if you are angry.
Show me your anger and tears.
Read it and find out how love-starting
revenge ends itself.
Someone already paid your bill.
Here you come!
Right at the time. Help me with the stuff.
-Hey Did you have supper? -No.
Thank you sister!
Don't mention it! No big deal.
It's my son. Handsome, right?
He is ill, sriously!
What is it? I can't remember what it is. The name is too long.
He got it from me. I was to balme.
I have to save him, whatever it takes.
Yes, come on.
It is happiness if I can be with him
even he is seriously sick.
Stop looking at me like that!
I promised San that I wouldn't cry for him anymore.
I was happy that he could be here with me.
That's what I think.
And then I can keep on.
Sorry, seeing you with San reminds me of my son.
And I got jealous.
I was just being petty.
No one wants a prosecutor under investigation.
And there are so many law school graduates, Attorneys are everywhere.
By the way, what's wrong with you
to get such a reputation?
It'll be hard for you to get a job anyway.
I need to see Mr. Jo Min Hyuk, could you please help me?
What's up?
I receieved this.
The debt that I should pay was transfered to you.
What's going on?
It means that you owe me money. Understand?
Well, I'm just...
I lost much to get rid of those creditors.
What are you looking at?
I'll definitely pay you back. Trust me.
We are going to be late. Hurry up!
Please believe me. I'll pay you back.
This is my phone number. I won't escape.
I'll pay you back, whatever it takes!
So, Please don't sell the Bakery. Please!
Oh, yes, the Bakery, is very important to you!
But that's why I bought it and I'm going to tear it down.
I told you so.
It's nothing, compared to what you did to me.
Sir, that's just... I..I know what's your relationship with Min Hyuk.
But, why you are here?
None of your business.
I am your fiancee. We are going to get married soon.
Last investigation and this debt affair,
I would feel really shameful if i were you!
Escort her out.
Right now!
Sir! sir!....
Sir! sir! Wait a minute!
What you said last time makes feel I would never see you again
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
Just, want to see a different world.
My world is suffocating.
I heard that you resigned.
I haven't had time to enjoy art before,
as I have to save time for law books.
I've worked hard not to fall behind.
But now I really understand why people come to galleries.
So, what's your feeling towards this one?
I wanna go there, if I can.
I like this paiting because I finished it in only one try.
If it was corrected many times, i would forget my innitiation.
And then, it's time to change the theme.
But I cannot do this.
Of course.
It is natural to think that it is a waste of time to think things can be better.
Are you talking about yourself?
You're not a good liar, Do Hoon!
-Are you OK? -Yes,
but I need to take them to my car quickly.
Give me! I will help you!
But, are you ok for not going to hospital?
- Yes. -Sorry.
Excuse me. We have to check these.
-Hello? -What?
Tolerating for a long time. What's the tolerance?
I told you! not mine!
A lady fell from a bike...
Don't make a story!
- By the way, you know me? - What?
Are you the hit-and-run? killing a mother and baby.
Yes, it's you.
You are breaking the law again in such a very short time out of jail.
I really cannot understand you.
Born on July 20th, right?
Not mine! I mean it!
How can we trust you?
Is there anyone who can vouch for you?
I really enjoyed your paintings thanks to you.
So see you next time.
I'm having a drink with some friends, would you like to join us?
You just left like that the other day.
-Se Yeon! -Hi!
-Are you finished? Where are we going? Who's this guy? -What?
Are you having an affair?
- What if Min Hyuk finds out? -We're not... - Yes.
That's right. That's what it is.
Min Hyuk likes scandal. Why not spread it?
- It does't look like so - Yes, we are,
if that's what Se Yeon thinks.
What?
Where are you going?
Come on, let's go together!
Yes. Girls drinking together can be boring.
What's your job?
What do you think he does?
He's currently out of work. But he was a civil servant not long before.
Uh...
How long have you been known each other?
Almost 4 years.
Black dress and red high heels.
You were drunk and yelling.
You asked me if I had enjoyed the show.
That was how we met, right?
The day we first met each other.
Do you remember that?
I do. I was a little drunk too.
The Shinhwa Hotel is elected to be the world polem.
Se Yeons can do everything.
It's not because of Se Yeon.
What? Are you standing up for your wife?
Uh, yes,
you don't have any frieng, either, right?
Why would I need friends?
Good for you, being a rich beggar without any friends.
But, anyway, I don't really know whether i should marry Se Yeon.
Don't be childish.
Your company isn't a mom and pop store.
A mere mistake you make will give you the rumor that you are not qulified to inHae Rit the big business and
they'll tear a strip off you.
- If you want to keep your position, you need Se Yeon. - I don't know.
- If you don't want her, can I have her? -What?
My family have always been pushing me have a second marriage.
I would really appreciate it if i can have Se Yeon as my wife.
Are you crazy? No way!
She deserves a guy way better than you and me.
I'm warning you. Stay away from her.
This sucks.
This is my phonenumber.
I won't escape.
I'll pay you back, whatever it takes!
So, Please don't sell the Bakery.
You have to pay me back anyway. Please!
Designated driver
I wanted to help a woman,
no, save her, exactly.
But, I failed.
And it is too late now.
The mere look at Se Yeon will remind me of that woman.
Do you think I am the man needing help?
Don't you?
The man who does't care won't here any rumors even if you spread them.
So, you'll have to show hime instead.
Do Hoon,
Thank you and....sorry.
I have no one to turn to.
You refused my offer of help, for distributing illegal flyers?
After asking Jo Min Hyuk for money, should you do this dirty job.
No, that's not what you think.
This is an organization for ex-convicts.
They'll find you a job.
It is you who wanted to breake up with me.
I do't want to see you again over something like this.
- Hello? -Designated driver - Hello!
- Come and pick me up - What?
Hey, Driver!
Driver Driver Driver
You drive the car!
I cannot drive!
My license was revoked.
Oh, yes, hit and run!
Then, why are you here?
You sounded really drunk, so I came to see if you are okay.
So were you worried?
Who do you think you are? Are you well enough to worry about me?
I'll call a driver for you.
No. Give me the keys!
Let me go.
No, don you want to be a man like me?
Where should I take you?
Wait a minute please!
Wake up, sir?
Did you have a good sleep?
Why are you here?
Don't you remember?
You were so drunk last night
that you couldn't tell me where you lived.
You had drunk to much.
Have some breakfast.
Do you expect me to eat this?
Eat before it gets cold.
And...
I've written down how I can pay off my debt.
I've been working really hard.
I think I can pay you off earlier than I thought.
About the bakery, can I...
Stop!
Water! Water!
Water！Uh, water!
Nobady pours water like you.
It's okay. Don't worry about me.
Stop smiling. Stop smiling in my face.
Unbelievable! This is unbelievable!
Sir!
Uh? This... you left this.
Your telephone was left in the car at the parking lot.
I am not troubling you!
This is coming off your debt.
Okay.
So what about the Bakery?
I'm not interested in seeing someone who turned down my offer.
I didn't know the K Corporation was interested in works of art
The K Culture Center is buying young artists' pieces in bulk at high prices..
And Shinhwa Gallery is the main dealing place.
And the Shinhwa Corporation gets billions of dollars in fees.
This is what I found over the last 2 years.
I really know how to keep a close relationship with Shinhwa.
Are you here to state the obvious?
The prosecution will definitely know waht i know.
If we do things for the cause of the country, everything's forgivable. And this is South Korea.
However, the K Corporation isn't a company that contributes to the country's economy.
And not a representation in this country in Export Industry.
In this perspective,
K Corporation is an easy target for the government.
Because they always need a scapegoat to divert people's attention.
Next week, they'll announce the sale of the Incheon Harbors facilities.
They're going to carry out another investigation on K.
And this time, the investigation will not focus only on the case.
If you've got your prey in your sights, why do you come to me?
I want you to give me another chance.
Why would I give you another chance
if the prosecution will finally know about this?
Knowing is strength.
I can protect you.
I won't let you sit in a wheelchair again.
Why did you change your mind?
Don't worry!
I'm not here to take your position.
I'll reach the top of the K Corporation.
I have fed up with the guys who can get everything without any efforts with their parents' money.
I'd like to see a guy like you, who worked hard to get here, win.
But listen.
The only person that President Jo wants to see succeeding is Jo Min Hyuk even if he beats Min Hyuk.
You can't be Min Hyuk.
No matter how hard you try, you're just a loyal dog that President Jo feeds.
So just wait and see.
I'm not like President Jo.
I don't think a man who can thorw away principles like you are trustworthy.
I will always keep a close eye on you.
Take care.
Oh my god! Yoo Jung.
Unbelievable! Nice seeing you here!
Do you know how I was worreid when
I heard that you lived here.
Hasn't she been mean to you?
No way, just the other way round. She is always naging me
not to drink too much and to get up early.
So don't drink too much and get up early.
Are you here on vocation?
Look, Yoo Jung!
If you don't feel comfortable staying here, or if you have a fight with her,
come to my place.
I live alone. I have no boyfriend. I will charge less.
Okay, Thank you.
By the way, where do we take these?
Where can we sell these?
Places like Dongdaemun Market? But we just bought these there.
Yoo Jung, this is...
Oh, how can you call it this or that?
Yoo Jung, don't use this or that.
Call it “my baby”.
Isn't my “baby” cute?
There are just so many big fans of our “baby”.
They're lined up for them.
Just leave Sellieg bain to us,
You can take your time moving the boxes
How should we recover the investment fund
to maintain the world polem?
It's said the CEO of Shenya Hotel is in charge on him own.
Why do we let the general manager do it?
To reverse the deficit of first half of the year.
We have to make sure polem get maintained.
Do we have a campaign for the second half?
I heard we have a problem in the terminal maintainence of polem.
Do you know that?
The committee was said to have already decided unofficially that they'd pick Shinhwa Hotel.
I guess you barely know that.
Should I reveal the names that chose Shinhwa?
Hello, Mr president? Can't you hear me?
Hello? Hello? President?
Shin Se Yeon!
Come on! You gotta meet friends?
I have something to celebrate and I need Se Yeon's bless.
So it's me who invited her.
Do I even need your permission to meet friends?
Friends?
Let's go. I have my car ready.
I'm a friend too.
I can be part of the celebration, can't I?
You are such a real friend,
to get Se Yeon here.
I asked her.
I don't get to see her paintings that often.
I thought you are not so shameless.
Prosecutor Ahn.
Oh, forgot it. You are not a prosecutor anymore.
Not easy to get a job in our company, right?
You are so excellent!
Thank you.
Of course you should go out with girls that match you.
Well, That's true.
If you have someone in mind,
save them for me.
Is there anyone like Se Yeon?
Se Yeon is my fiancee.
Since you are working in K Corporation,
she is your boss.
Mind your manners.
She is not the kind of woman that you deserve.
Oh, you should know that.
Then why would you treat her as some random girl?
Like you just said,
Se Yeon can't be treated like that.
I don't think
you have any right to say anything about our relationship.
You are the one who is mean to her! Jo Min Hyuk
I wanna take her from you
even if I know I don't deserve her.
Don't you think you are what I am
for drinking with me.
No matter how you got in my company,
I'm you boss.
And nothing can change that
You are still not going anywhere even I give you a treat like this.
It can't be more obvious.
Days of free-ride can be.
It's obviously shameless to enjoy all you have
with your parents' money?
How dare you say that?
Jo Min Hyuk! Are you here to have a fight?
Haven't you heard what he said?
It's ok.
He said nothing wrong.
I don't think it's okay.
He is my guest.
I don't want him to be unhappy.
You still cook?
Once in a while.
You've never cooked for me.
You've never asked me.
It's great, Se Yeon.
I don't think he doesn't have feelings for you.
He does, as men see it.
You are such a good actor, Do Hoon!
I thought you don't lie.
A girl who you want to take away from him?
That wasn't a lie.
Now I could understand why people in TV series fall in love an get married in real life.
If you are too into the characters,
that can happen.
Oops, so hot!
]What?
You want me to drink this?
Nothing is better than this after exhausting work.
It's too sweet.
Whatever.
Besides, are you kidding me?
30 years?
Do you think I would keep seeing you for 30 years
simply for the little money.
Well it's big money for me.
I promise I'd work hard,
So I'll be able to pay up a few years earlier.
A few years?
No way.
You said you had a boyfriend.
Why don't you ask him for some help?
What now?
Dumped?
Right?
Of course you are.
An ex-criminal with big debt to pay?
Who would take her?
He is not the kind man.
Fuck that, he surely is.
Going out as if you are the one to him,
and slipping away as long as you bring up marriage.
Aren't the guys you went out with all like that?
I said he is not!
I am an ex criminal with a huge debt,
but we didn't break up for that.
He isn't the kind of man that you said.
Even after we broke up,
when I did something stupid,
he took me to a hospital to save me.
He's been caring for me all the time quietly.
He just left quietly in case I get guilty.
Hey, that was...
So, don't think you know everything.
Ahn Do Hoon.
I had no idea you are so great.
This is all my savings
and my pension.
Pension?
I am in the Legal Team of K Corporation.
The pay is great.
Do Hoon, are you sure about your decision?
Yes
I'm not giving up my dream.
I chose this not to give up my dream.
I found a good location for a restaurant.
You should go check it.
Restaurant?
Don't work for anybody.
I would give the money you need.
You would rest even if I tell you to.
And that's why I say this.
You've been quarreling all you life.
I would never wanna see
You live the life suffering because of me,
the life taking care of me only.
The money won't be wasted
only if it's given to parents.
Mom, I like this one.
That's for the eldly.
How about this one?
I want this one,
and the red one. I want both.
Just take one of them.
Why?
You barely use them!
It would be a waste of money for you.
All my friends have so many of them that they don't know
which one to choose when they go out.
I'm gonna tell your father that
you skip classes and come here if insist.
Mother!
Now you are like my step-mother.
Min Joo, your friends' parents buy them everything
because they don't care about them
How about let me find you someone,
and buy you a better one?
Really?
Did mom want me to buy a knockoff?
Miss, this isn't an ordinary knockoff.
We used the same leather with the real one,
and the stitches are class A,
and a Chinese craftsman made every stitch carefully...
Oh my princess, you are so pretty.
You are truly right.
It is a knockoff.
But who would know that?
It depends completely on how you see it.
Princess, please close your eyes.
1,2,3.
Now look at this one.
Ok, it really suits you.
Try to empty your mind.
123 open your eyes!
You can see it right? Beautiful line and glossy facade.
Oh my pretty child.
Look at the glossy facade.
No one could match me.
Look at it!
No matter what, this kind of bag…
Min Joo.
Isn't it great to have a lot of bags,
and use a different one everyday?
And you could get relaxed.
And people would take the knockoff as real ones and envy you.
Isn't it a lot of fun?
Mrs. Hong. Long time no see. You look younger than ever.
Sandra Wang, it's been a long time.
Right, I went to New York, San Francisco
because of work.
Guys, come and meet our Mrs Hong.
You know me, right?
Yes.
This is unbelievable! How dare you come back here?
What are you doing here?
It's not what you think.
You are so ridiculous.
You sold my ring,
and how dare you come back to my house?
You're such a cunning girl with innocent appearance.
Min Hyuk really does have weird tastes.
What are you doing here?
What are you doing?
Min Hyuk,
Do you hang out with girls all like this?
No, we don't have the kind of relationship.
What do you mean by girls like this?
Do I even have to spell that out?
Isn't it obvious? She wants your money!
You can't meet Min Hyuk anymore.
I am not a man with know manner.
I don't know what I would do.
What do you think you're doing?
I know men want to play around before getting married.
But Min Hyuk you can't date with anybody.
You don't have the right to say that.
You wanted my father's money,
Woman comes here like she is waiting my mother to die
doesn't have the right to say that.
Let's go.
Are you crazy? How dare you come here?
I didn't know this is your house.
Is this what you've been doing to pay my debt?
See you again, my friend.
Excuse me,
we have something urgent to talk about.
By the way, did you get the present
I sent you?
Hope you like it.
Want a drink?
Not in the mood, drinking in daytime.
You know Prosecutor Ahn, don't you?
Wait! He started working for our legal team
after resigning as a prosecutor.
He's Attorney An now.
Didn't you know?
Look at your face!
Do yo have any affairs or what?
No.
He is my friend.
Seems I got a good friend because of you.
What? Is it strange to find we are friends?
Attorney An looked surprised to find we are together.
Yes? I'll be right there.
I won't be here anymore.
You need to have a philosophy
and an eye for beauty to sell our products, don't you?
Sis, don't forget. Seventy thirty, I got seventy.
How about stewed intestines and spirits?
Hey!
Do you know what you are doing? Do you know who he is?
Yes.
And you are still doing this?
What about you?
You quitted
and work for him. What does that mean?
I heard you are friends.
Friends? Yeah.
A toy he could play with as his will could also be called a friend.
Quitting and working for him is not my will only.
I don't want to talk about that anymore. What's your plan?
I got debt to pay.
I heard that my debt was transferred to him.
I don't know how it happened.
Yoo Jung, pull yourself together.
There are reasons for him not letting go of you.
But I still have to pay the debt.
Do you know what he's done?
He must hate me. He must despise me.
Don't be so stupid.
We have already paid for what we did.
Last 4 years has been so terribly sad.
Listen to me.
I'm worried about you. You leave him now.
I'll find out about the debt, and I'll make you know.
Lee Hye Jin!
Shit. Stop it. I'm not running away.
I won't run.
Just give me a punch.
Isn't that why you are after me?
Shit. I can't believe we meet like this.
Punch you? Could that bring San back to me?
Ok, if that's what you want.
You can have it no matter how much you want it.
What are you talking about?
You bitch.
What the fuck.
Why?
The hell you.
What is it? What happened to San?
What do you mean?
San…
is dead.
That was the last time I held him in my arms.
At first I was thinking what do I do if I meet you again.
Every night, I tried to find what to do to feel better.
Time just passed by.
Why... in the end, I just wanna know why...
Why did you do that to me and San.
Why…
I don't know. Not as much as you did, but I loved San.
I mean it. They said San would be okay.
They wanted me to stop you from getting your parole.
My parole？
I was manipulated.
Yoo Jung, did you make someone really angry?
Do you know what Min Hyuk did?
Enjoy your time in jail.
You are gonna be so miserable after you get out.
You should suffer what I suffered.
Lose you loved ones and there's nothing you can do.
Next on Secret Love
Look at this.
What?
What's the matter?
You said you saw someone fall down there and just leave him there alone, right?
Are these really a woman's footprint?
It was the day the accident happened to Xu.
If Attorney An knows how much I know about Attorney An…
that might be a big shock.
Is there a copy of the file in the black box of accident car.
Could you please do me a favor?
Did you really just left after you saw the accident
without doing anything.